Okay, in the meantime, let's bring the stock of Polis to
your screen where the numbers have come up. The
company has posted a profit of Rs
402 crore. Although the expectations were that the profit would be around Rs 270 crore, so this figure is more than the expectations. This figure has been seen coming on the profitability front. The revenue numbers that have come up are around Rs 3890 crore. The
company has posted a revenue of
around Rs 32 crore. So,
prima facie, two figures have
come up. Both profitability and revenue have been
much higher than the expectations on every side
and perhaps that is why the stock is also
seeing a rise. If you
compare it with the same quarter of last year, then also there has been a
growth of 70-80% in the profit of the company. The
company has posted a profit of Rs 400 plus crore, increasing from Rs 222 crore and the profit has
also increased from Rs 2736 crore to around Rs 3890 crore. So, the
numbers, at present, the
margins will have to be seen, but the
numbers are looking good.
Polycap has already crossed almost 4000, let's take quicklayer comments also,
here from the numbers sofa expectation,
son, what is the positive reaction on the stock
from the view level,
its target which was
4000, is near the same level, I would
advise you to book profit from here for the near term
and we can get back near 3800, if we get there then we can
return, yes
ok, so now in fact it is not above 4000, it is
decisively trying to go above the
levels of 4000-13, when will it shift and
after the numbers come above the day, if you react then
good numbers and that is why
we should see this kind of reaction in the stock, 4015, this is
Polycap from Mercedes level, let's
bring another stock in the meantime, that is Delta Corp
and see the stock, days have gone hyper, in
fact, from today onwards there is also a rise in Fino Ban, five
days ago the level of 192, especially in the last 10-15
minutes, this  A tremendous rally has been
seen divided in the stock, what is
your suggestion, Delta Corp has
formed a double bottom kid of formation from these levels, 175
levels and according to this formation, it is
definitely a reversal,
according to me, this oxide and
you can go up, this stock
is bought from here, a little below the current level, a
stoppage of 180 should be placed on the upper side, this is an
possibility, the list of 220 levels from 2015
can show in the near term that there is
full possibility and if there are buying positions
then you can hold, but
you are seeing strong momentum Delta,
let's stop for a break, there is an
interesting news, we will tell you, in fact, the
insurance company will soon compensate for the losses caused by the floods in North India, what are the
complete details